WORAROJ SURUXRUTTANASKUL

691 W33rd, Vancouver Tel: +66 98-842-1676 Email: wrj.ss@icloud.com

## **PROFILE**

Hi my name is Chin Su 27 years old junior-mid web frontend developer graduated WMAD from Cornerstone Community College of Canada, currently working as a freelance frontend developer and temporary frontend developer at Al Technovation Co.,Ltd using Javascript ES6, React.js, Next.js Hooks and Redux with styled-components. Constantly working and learning web technologies and other design related topics and I'm a skilled in many areas of development and design . Some of my skills include are really basic but i trying to learn and improve it. With a passion for create and develop in Content and Website and Mobile App, i have both the kill and knowledge to dive deep into the world. As a self-motivated team player with both communication in English and Thai.

## **SKILLS**

- JAVASCRIPT ES6, REACT.JS, NEXT.JS, Hooks, REDUX

- Content Management System (Strapi). - HTML, CSS AND JAVASCRIPT

- VERSION CONTROL (GITHUB, GITLAB) - ADOBE XD

- BOOTSTRAP, REACTSTRAP, Styled-components - ENGLISH - THAI

# **EDUCATION**

CO-OP DIPLOMA IN WEB AND MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

- CORNERSTONE COMMUNITY COLLEGE | VANCOUVER | B.C. | CANADA | 2017 - 2018

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

- DUSIT THANI COLLEGE | BANGKOK | THAILAND | 2013-2016

INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM

- BELMONT SECONDARY SCHOOL | VICTORIA | CANADA | 2011

## **EXPERIENCE**

# FREELANCE FRONT-END DEVELOPER | NEXT.JS, HEADLESS CMS (STRAPI) FREELANCE VANCOUVER CA, CALIFORNIA USA, BANGKOK THAILAND | 2021

Working directly from client from design mock-ups and storyboards to real and responsive user interface. Most of the clients are from recommend by previous client that I use to work with and some are from oversea connection.

# WEB FRONT-END DEVELOPER | NEXT.JS, HEADLESS CMS (STRAPI) AI TECHNOVATION CO.,LTD BANGKOK THAILAND | 2020-2021

Responsible for planing, managing and develop UX/UI and content management systems for client self management a content for the site. Working directly with client and designer and I have a opportunity to be a consultant for junior and front-end trainee to be on the same standard. Most of the site here were NEXT.JS with styled-components and build as a SSG and client site fetching to our CMS platform on HEROKU.

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER | REACT ES6, HOOKS AND REDUX NELLIKA CONSULTING CO.,LTD VANCOUVER B.C.- BANGKOK THAILAND | 2019-2020

Responsible for develop user interface website working closely with designer team. Using React with JS ES6 Hooks and Redux with styled-components, develop from mock-ups and storyboards to real and responsive user interface. And working closely with the team by using version controls like GitHub and GitLab. Also working with Adobe XD illustrator for design layout and flow of the Website. Create and optimize content for Website using a variety of graphics, database, animation and other Library. Develop Website architecture and determine hardware and software requirements.